Guide to the Yale Summer Cabaret Scripts and Ephemera Collection
Yale University Arts Library
Yale Summer Cabaret Scripts and Ephemera Collection
1974-2016
DRA 35
Yale University Arts Library
4.75
(10 boxes)
This collection contains scripts and ephemera from the Yale Summer Cabaret (formerly known as the Ensemble Company for the Performing Arts).
Yale University. Summer Cabaret
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Yale Summer Cabaret Scripts and Ephemera Collection was housed in the former Drama Library until its transfer to the Robert B. Haas Family Arts Library in 2008. The 2014 addition, which included materials for the period 1974 through 2014, was a gift of Don Lowy on behalf of the Yale Summer Cabaret Advisory Board. The 2015 addition was also delivered by Don Lowy on behalf of the Yale Summer Cabaret Advisory Board.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains scripts and ephemera, such as programs, flyers, and posters, as well as photographs from the Yale Summer Cabaret.
Biographical / Historical
The Yale Summer Cabaret is a wholly separate organization from the Yale Cabaret. It has been in operation since 1974. From 1974 until 2008, it was known as the Ensemble Company for the Performing Arts or ECPA (also referred to as the Ensemble Company for the Creative Arts). ECPA was dissolved on May 16, 2008, and absorbed by the Yale School of Drama. Yale Summer Cabaret has, since its inception, been managed by Yale School of Drama students. It stages three to four productions per summer in a venue with under 100 reconfigurable seats. Food and drink are served before each performance. Yale Summer Cabaret produces adaptations of published plays, student-written plays, and collaboratively devised pieces.
A detailed history of Yale Summer Cabaret productions is available in the repository. This documentation has been compiled and provided by Don Lowy on behalf of the YSC Executive Board (last updated September 22, 2014).
Arrangement
Organized into two series and one addition: I. Scripts. II. Ephemera. 2014 Addition.
Scripts (documents); Photographs; Press releases; Theater programs; Fliers (printed matter); Yale Summer Cabaret; Ensemble Company for the Performing Arts; Ensemble Company for the Creative Arts
- Scripts, Series I
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically by season, then alphabetically by the playwright's last name.
  - The 1940s Radio Hour, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Mojo Candy, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Out of Synch, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Great Solo Town, 1977 (Box 1)
  - The Comedy of Errors, 1977 (Box 1)
  - A Hunger Artist, 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1919: A Baseball Opera, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Division Street, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Criminals in Love, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Get It While You Can, 1994 (Box 1)
  - The Shawl, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Summer Cabaret 1994 Production Book (Box 3)
    General note
    Oversize
  - Bad Intentions, 1997 (Box 2)
  - The Metamorphosis, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Valparaiso, 2001 (Box 2)
  - No Exit, 2001 (Box 2)
- Ephemera
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes ephemera such as posters, programs, photographs, clippings, advertisements, press releases, and newsletters pertaining to ECPA and Yale Summer Cabaret.
  Arranged chronologically by year and then by month and day of performance.
  - ECPA ephemera, 1974, Folder 1: 12 items; Folder 2: 7 items; Folder 3: 10 items (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1975, Folder 4: 11 items; Folder 5: 24 items; Folder 6: 20 items; Folder 7: 15 items; Folder 8: 15 items (Box 4, Folder 4-8)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1976, 12 items (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1977, 13 items (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1978, Folder 11: 11 items; Folder 12: 12 items (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1979, 13 items (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1980, 8 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1981, 13 items (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1982, 10 items (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1983, 8 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1984, 9 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1985, 16 items (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1986, 10 items (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1987, 9 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1988, 6 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1989, 11 items (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1990, Folder 24: 10 items; Folder 25: 11 items (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1991, 11 items (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1992, 17 items (Box 5, Folder 27)
    There was no Summer Cabaret in 1993.
  - ECPA ephemera, 1994, Folder 28: 11 items; Folder 29: 10 items; Folder 30: 8 items (Box 5, Folder 28-30)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1995, 13 items (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1996, Folder 32: 12 items; Folder 33: 11 items; Folder 34: 41 items (Box 5, Folder 32-34)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1997, Folder 35: 12 items; Folder 36: 14 items (Box 5, Folder 35-36)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1998, 7 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - ECPA ephemera, 1999, 14 items (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - ECPA ephemera, 2000, Folder 39: 11 items; Folder 40: 10 items; Folder 41: 10 items; Folder 42: 8 items; Folder 43: 9 items; Folder 44: 11 items; Folder 45: 12 items (Box 5, Folder 39-45)
  - ECPA ephemera, 2001, Folder 46: 10 items; Folder 47: 10 items; Folder 48: 14 items (Box 6, Folder 46-48)
  - ECPA ephemera, 2002, Folder 49: 10 items; Folder 50: 11 items (Box 6, Folder 49-50)
  - ECPA ephemera, 2003, 12 items (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - ECPA ephemera, 2004, Folder 52: 11 items; Folder 53: 7 items (Box 6, Folder 52-53)
  - ECPA ephemera, 2005, Folder 54: 10 items; Folder 55: 11 items (Box 6, Folder 54-55)
  - ECPA ephemera, 2006, 10 items (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - ECPA ephemera, 2007, Folder 57: 10 items; Folder 58: 12 items; Folder 59: 10 items; Folder 60: 11 items; Folder 61: 11 items (Box 6, Folder 57-61)
  - ECPA ephemera, 2008, Folder 62: 11 items; Folder 63: 13 items; Folder 64: 10 items (Box 6, Folder 62-64)
    This year marks the end of the ECPA. It was dissolved on May 16, 2008, and was absorbed by the Yale School of Drama.
  - Summer Cabaret ephemera, 2009, 10 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- 2014 Addition, 1974-2014
  The 2014 addition includes programs and flyers, photographs, original scripts, and posters.
  Each grouping of materials is arranged chronologically by season.
  - Programs, Posters, and Flyers, 1974-2014
    This subseries contains season flyers and posters as well as programs and posters for individual shows. It also includes some reproductions of these materials (as noted).
    - 1974 season, 8 (Box 7, Folder 66)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 1 season poster (in reproduction); 5 show programs; 1 show poster
      Shows represented:
      The Marriage of Bette & Boo, Christopher Durang
      Zee Learned Ladies, Moliere
      "Wilde!," Oscar Wilde
      The 1940 Radio Hour, Walton Jones
      Much Ado About Nothing, William Shakespeare
    - 1975 season, 2 (Box 7, Folder 67)
      Includes: 1 season flyer (with menu) and 1 season poster (in reproduction)
    - 1976 season, 7 (Box 7, Folder 68)
      Includes: 2 season flyers; 5 show programs; 1 show poster (in reproduction)
      The Importance of Being Earnest, Oscar Wilde
      Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, Stevens
      Measure for Measure, William Shakespeare
    - 1977 season, 3 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      Includes: 1 season poster; 2 show programs
      God, Woody Allen
      The 1940's Radio Show: Middle-of-the-War Show
    - 1978 season, 14 items (Box 7, Folder 70)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 1 "As You Like It" menu; 8 show posters; and 4 show programs
      Death, Woody Allen
      The Bat, Mary Roberts Rinehart and Avery Hopwood
      Overruled, George Bernard Shaw
      The Misanthrope, Moliere
      The Madman & The Nun, S. W. Witkiewicz
      Interludes, Allan Havis
      Twelfth Night, William Shakespeare
    - 1979 season, 2 (Box 7, Folder 71)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 1 program
      Happy End, Kurt Weill
    - 1980 season, 24 items (Box 7, Folder 72)
      Includes: 3 season flyers; 10 show posters; 10 show programs; and 1 Children's Theatre Workshop flyer
      Die Fledermaus, Johan Strauss
      The Critic, Richard Brinsley Sheridan
      Love Yourself Above All Others, Jorge Diaz
      Sganarelle II, Moliere
      Sexual Perversity in Chicago, David Mamet
      Benten Kozo
      Back By Popular Demand: Sexual Perversity in Chicago,
      In the Zone, Eugene O'Neill
      Prelude to a Kiss: An Evening of Duke Ellington Songs
      Children's shows represented:
      The Quasar Conspiracy
    - 1981 season, 17 items (Box 7, Folder 73)
      Includes: 2 season flyers; 15 show programs (includes duplicates)
      The Real Inspector Hound, Tom Stoppard
      Two Gentleman of Verona, William Shakespeare
      Double Bill: Mozart & Salieri, Alexander Pushkin, Translated by A.F.B. Clark; I'm Dreaming, But Am I?, Luigi Pirandello
      1919: A Baseball Opera, Conceived & Written by Rusty Magee & Rob Barron. Music by Rusty Magee
      Orpheus, Jean Cocteau, Adapted by Lynn Siefert
      Interview, Jean-Claude Van Italie
      The Exception and The Rule, Bertolt Brecht
      Private Lives, Noel Coward
    - 1982 season, 11 items (Box 7, Folder 74)
      Includes: 3 season flyers; 1 season poster; 6 show programs; 1 show poster
      À Jacques Brel: A Tribute to the Great Belgian Chanteur
      The Comedy of Errors, William Shakespeare
      The Dumb Waiter, Harold Pinter
      Under Milkwood, Dylan Thomas
      And the Band Played On, An Original Musical by Lisa Fisher and Diane Wynter
    - 1983 season, 11 items (Box 7, Folder 75)
      Includes: 3 season flyers; 8 show programs
      Sondheim!: Music of Stephen Sondheim
      The Good Doctor, Neil Simon
      Son of Arlecchino, Leon Katz
      Pvt. Wars, James McLure
      Oklahoma O.K., Adapted by Grafton Mouen and Michael Zelenak
      The Patient, Agatha Christie
    - 1984 season, 4 (Box 7, Folder 76)
      Includes: 3 season flyers; 1 program
      Sister Mary Ignatius Explains It All To You, Christopher Durang
    - 1985 season, 11 items (Box 7, Folder 77)
      Includes: 3 season flyers; 1 season poster; 7 show programs
      Tintypes, Mary Kyte with Gary Pearle
      Flash Gordon Conquers the Planet of Evil, L. Lewis Stout
      Lone Star, James McClure
      Tintypes (Reprise)
      U.S. Oh!, Conceived by Evan Yionoulis
      The Art of Dining, Tina Howe
      Heavenzapoppin, Dick Beebe
      The Girl of the Golden West, David Belasco, Adapted by Phyllis Look
    - 1986 season, 9 (Box 7, Folder 78)
      Includes: 3 season flyers; 6 show programs
      Starting Here, Starting Now!, Matlby & Shire
      Berlin to Broadway with Kurt Weill, Music by Kurt Weill, Text by Gene Lerner
      Pins & Needles, Harold Rome
      The Birthday Party, Harold Pinter
      Division Street, Steve Tesich
    - 1987 season, 9 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      Pathological Venus, Brighde Mullins
      El Grande de Coca-Cola, Ron House, John Neville- Andrews, Alan Shearman, Diz White and Sally Willis
      Life Under Water, Richard Greenberg
      The Sin of Akaki Akakiyevich, Elizabeth Egloff
      The Juniper Tree: A Tragic Household Tale, Written & Composed by Wendy Kesselman
      Mahagonny Songspiel, Bertolt Brecht and Kurt Weill
    - 1988 season, 17 items (Box 7, Folder 80)
      Includes: 3 season flyers; 7 show posters (includes 1 original paste-up); 7 show programs (all original paste-ups)
      To Glenda, From Fred, Gil Kofman
      Jungle Toons, Bernardo Solano
      Airport Angel, Bill Corbett
      The True History of Napoleon the Great
      The Miracle Play, Michael Fields
      The Rendezvous, Mark Levin
      The House of Yes, Wendy MacLeod
    - 1989 season, 3 (Box 7, Folder 81)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 2 show programs
      Somebody Else, Miklos Vamos
      Solo Flight, John Reaves
    - 1990 season, 5 (Box 7, Folder 82)
      Includes: 5 show programs
      Duck Variations, David Mamet
      'dentity Crisis, Christopher Durang
      Courtship, Reaves
      Orchards, Anton Chekhov
      The Harold, Del Close
    - 1991 season, 14 items (Box 7, Folder 83)
      Includes: 3 season flyers; 3 show posters; 8 show programs
      The Wedding, Bertolt Brecht
      Cinema Massacre, Boris Vian
      Tatlin's Tower, Evan Yionoulis & Thomas Cabaniss
      The System of Doctor Tarr & Professor Fether, Audré Lorde
      The Great American U.F.P. Special Election Super Show, Daniel Rubin
    - 1992 season, 11 items (Box 7, Folder 84)
      Includes: 2 season flyers; 1 season poster; 6 show programs; 2 show posters
      Criminals in Love, George F. Walker
      The Baltimore Waltz, Paula Vogel
      Slave Island, Pierre Marivaux
      7 Blowjobs, Mac Wellman
      Outside the Door, Wolfgang Borchert
    - 1994 season, 13 items (Box 7, Folder 85)
      Includes: 1 invitation (YSC 20th Anniversary Gala Dinner); 5 season flyers (4 in reproduction); 4 show programs (1 in reproduction); 3 show posters (3 in reproduction)
      The Shawl, David Mamet
      Other Places, Harold Pinter
      Endgame, Samuel Beckett
      Get It While You Can, Julie McKee
    - 1995 season, 7 (Box 7, Folder 86)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 6 show programs
      Double Bill: Screaming Laughter: The Rats, Agatha Christie, Wooed & Viewed, Georges Feydeau
      The Tempest, Shakespeare
      Double Bill: Shawtime! How He Lied to Her Husband, George Bernard Shaw, Overruled, George Bernard Shaw
      The Fattest Man in the World Lives Upstairs, Janet Malia Allard
    - 1996 season, 5 (Box 7, Folder 87)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 4 show programs
      Three Weeks After Marriage, Arthur Murphy
      A Dose of Durang, (Four Short Plays by Durang)
      Faithful, Chazz Palminteri
      If Only, Jeffrey B. Teitler
    - 1997 season, 7 (Box 7, Folder 88)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 1 1997 passport handbook; 1 "Remember When...?" flyer; 4 show programs (1 in reproduction)
      Helen!: A Farce Bearing Some Resemblance to the Play by Euripides, Adapted by Preston Lane
      The Handwriting, The Soup and The Hats, Suzanne Maynard
      Billy Bishop Goes To War, John Gray
      Bad Intentions, Wade McIntyre
    - 1998 season, 5 (Box 7, Folder 89)
      Gravity Calling, Diane Flacks (American Premiere)
      The Bald Soprano & Foursome, Eugene Ionesco
      The Vampire, J.R. Planche, Adapted by David Kennedy, Music by Sean McClowry
      Against the Grain, From the novel by J.K. Huysmans, Text by James Krouse, Music by Sean McClowry (WORLD PREMIERE)
    - 1999 season, 6 (Box 7, Folder 90)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 1 season poster; 4 show programs
      The Sisterhood, Moliere, Translated & Adapted by Ranjit Bolt
      Maggie Cassidy, Chris Jeffries
      The Turn of the Screw, Jeffrey Hatcher
      A Bob Called Hope, Brian W. Robinson
    - 2000 season, 8 (Box 7, Folder 91)
      Includes: 2 season flyers; 1 season poster (in reproduction?); 4 show programs
      Poor Folk's Pleasure, Len Jenkin
      The Metamorphosis, Franz Kafka, Adapted by Leslie Kramer
      Beyond Therapy, Christopher Durang
      The Mystery of Irma Vep, Charles Ludlam
    - 2001 season, 4 (Box 7, Folder 92)
      Includes: 4 show programs
      Valparaiso, Don DeLillo
      bash: latterday plays, Neil LaBute
      No Exit, Jean Paul Sartre
      ART, Yasmina Resa
    - 2002 season, 6 (Box 7, Folder 93)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 1 show poster; 4 show programs
      A Midsummer Night's Dream, Shakespeare
      Hot and Throbbing, Paula Vogel
      Private Eyes, Steven Dietz
      Three Days of Rain, Richard Greenberg
    - 2003 season, 4 (Box 7, Folder 94)
      The Ten Thousand Things, Melissa James Gibson
      Livin Tired, Marcus Gardley
      The Home, Jami O'Brien
      Leah's Train, Karen Hartman
    - 2004 season, 6 (Box 7, Folder 95)
      Cabaret, John Kander, Fred Ebb, Joe Masteroff
      The Tempest, William Shakespeare
      10 New Plays: Crappy Reasons, Jami O'Brien; The Ten Minute Play About Rosemary's Baby, Roberto Aquirre-Sacasa; Hipsterville, Victor Kaufold; Jade Flowerpots and Bound Feet, David Henry Hwang; Pops, Edwin Sanchez; None of the Above, Aron and Michael Egner; Psyche in Love, Wendy Wasserstein; Big Dave, Sunil Kuruvilla; I Call Your Name, Tim Acito; And All I Got Was This Lousy T-shirt, Alena Smith
      …and Jesus Moonwalks on the Mississippi, Marcus Gardley
    - 2005 season, 4 (Box 7, Folder 96)
      Woyzeck, Georg Buchner
      Piano Plays, Frederike Roth, Self-Accusation, Peter Handke
      Preparadise, Sorry Now, Rainer Werner Fassbinder
      Baal, Bertolt Brecht
    - 2006 season, 9 (Box 7, Folder 97)
      Includes: 2 season posters; 3 show posters; 4 show programs
      The War is Over, Nastaran Ahmadi
      Savage/Love & Tongues, Sam Shepard & Joseph Chaikin
      Zero Hour, Tea Alagic
      The New Tenant, Eugene Ionesco
    - 2007 season, 6 (Box 7, Folder 98)
      Includes: 1 show poster; 1 newspaper clipping; 1 postcard; 3 show programs (1 in reproduction)
      God is a DJ, Falk Richter
      The Pornographic Angel, Nelson Rodrigues
      EYE, Alex Knox
    - 2008 season, 1 (Box 7, Folder 99)
      Includes: 1 program
      Kids These Days, Michael Barker, Joe Kendall, Chris Quinn
    - 2009 season, 7 (Box 7, Folder 100)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 3 show posters (in reproduction?); 3 show programs
      Late: A Cowboy Song, Sarah Ruhl
      Fly-by-night, Will Connolly, Michael Mitnick, Kim Rosenstock
    - 2010 season, 8 (Box 7, Folder 101)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 1 season poster (in reproduction); 3 show posters; 3 show programs
      Hedwig and the Angry Inch, John Cameron Mitchell, Stephen Trask
      The Phoenix, Isobelle Carmody
      muse, Brenna Palughi
    - 2011 season, 2 (Box 7, Folder 102)
      Includes: 2 show programs
      As You Like It, William Shakespeare
      Rose Mark'd Queen, adapted from Henry V, Henry VI (Part 1, 2 and 3) and Richard III
    - 2012 season, 5 (Box 7, Folder 103)
      Includes: 1 season flyer; 3 show posters (in reproduction); 1 program
      The K of D, Laura Schellhardt
      Of Ogres Retold, conceived by Adam Rigg
      The Secret in the Wings, Mary Zimmerman
    - 2013 season, 16 items (Box 7, Folder 104)
      Includes: 2 season flyers (in reproduction); 2 season posters (in reproduction); 7 show posters (in reproduction); 5 show programs
      Tartuffe, Moliere
      Miss Julie, Strindberg
      The Shoemaker's Prodigious Wife, Lorca
      In the Bar of a Tokyo Hotel, Williams
      Double Bill: Hearts Desire, Caryl Churchill, and Drunk Enough to Say I Love You, Caryl Churchill
    - 2014 season, 9 (Box 7, Folder 105)
      Includes: 2 season flyers; 7 show programs
      Why Torture Is Wrong, And The People Who Love Them, Christopher Durang
      A Map of Virtue, Erin Courtney
      We Are Proud To Present A Presentation About The Herero Of Namibia, Formerly Known As Southwest Africa, From The German Sudwestafrika, Between The Years 1884 – 1915, Jackie Sibblies Drury
      Middletown, Will Eno
      Summer Shorts: Series A: Ron Bobby Had Too Big A Heart, Rolin Jones; M.A.H. (A Museum Play), Kate Tarker; Another In A Long Line Of Idiot Children, Rolin Jones; Excerpt from Undesirables, Book/Lyrics by Hansol Jung, Music by Chris Bannow
      Summer Shorts: Series B: The Mercury And The Magic, Rolin Jones; We Have Cookies, Rey Pamatmat; Your Living Room Is Full Of Ghosts, MJ Kaufman; All Saints, Mary Laws
  - Photographs, 1974-2013
    Arranged chronologically by season.
    This subseries contains original photographs from Yale Summer Cabaret rehearsals, productions, promotions, etc.
    - 1974 season photographs, 31 photographs (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - 1975 season photographs, 45 photographs (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - 1976 season photographs, 14 photographs (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - 1977 season photographs, 4 photographs (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - 1978 season photographs, 21 photographs (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - 1979 season photographs, 7 photographs (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - 1980 season photographs, 3 photographs (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - 1981 season photographs, 19 photographs (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - 1984 season photographs, 13 photographs (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - 1985 season photographs, 18 photographs (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - 1987 season photographs, 1 photograph (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - 1988 season photographs, 8 photographs (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - 1989 season photographs, 8 photographs (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - 1990 season photographs, 5 photographs (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - 1991 season photographs, 3 photographs (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - 1994 season photographs, 9 photographs (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - 1995 season photographs, 3 photographs (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - 1996 season photographs, 5 photographs (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - 1997 season photographs, 6 photographs (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - 1998 season photographs, 1 photograph (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - 2000 season photographs, 8 photographs (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - 2001 season photographs, 28 photographs (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - 2006 season photographs, 6 photographs (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - 2007 season photographs, 3 photographs (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - 2008 season photographs, 2 photographs (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - 2013 season photographs, 1 photograph (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Scripts, 1988-2006
    This subseries contains 16 original scripts from YSC productions.
    Arranged chronologically by season. Dates indicate season of production.
    - The Rendezvous, 1998; 1 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Airport Angel, 1988; 1 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - The House of Yes, 1988; 1 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Courtship, 1990; 1 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - 3 Weeks After Marriage, 1996; 1 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - The Handwriting, The Soup and the Hats, 1997; 1 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Helen (adaptation from Euripedes), 1997; 1 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - A Bob Called Hope, 1999; 1 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Livin Tired, 2003; 1 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - The Ten Thousand Things, 2003; 1 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Leah's Train, 2003; 1 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - The Home, 2003; 1 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Tongues, 2006; 1 (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - The War Is Over, 2006; 1 (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - Zero Hour, 2006; 1 (Box 9, Folder 146)
    - The New Tenant (possible adaptation), 2006; 1 (Box 9, Folder 147)
  - Posters, 1975-2014
    This subseries contains original season and show posters for the Yale Summer Cabaret.
    Materials are housed, however, in reverse chronological order.
    - 1975 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1977 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1983 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1983 show poster for Sondheim!, 2 (Box 10, Folder 148)
      Includes June 8-11 poster and June 29-July 2 encore poster.
    - 1983 show poster for Son of Arlecchino, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1983 show poster for Pvt. Wars, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1983 show poster for Oklahoma OK!, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1983 show poster for The Patient, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1984 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1984 show poster for Nice Work If You Can Get It: An Evening with George and Ira Gershwin, 2 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1984 show poster for Sister Mary Ignatius Explains It All To You, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1984 show poster for Oh, Cloris!, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1984 show poster for Suicide in B flat, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1984 show poster for Cops, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1985 show poster for Tintypes, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1985 show poster for Lone Star, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1990 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1992 show poster for The Baltimore Waltz, 2 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1992 show poster for 7 Blowjobs, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1992 show poster for Outside the Door, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1994 show poster for The Shawl, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)